{
  "list": [
    {
      "question": "toll",
      "answer": "稅",
    },
    {
      "question": "precious",
      "answer": "珍貴的",
    },
    {
      "question": "prosperous",
      "answer": "繁榮的",
    },
    {
      "question": "asset",
      "answer": "資產",
    },
    {
      "question": "opulence",
      "answer": "富裕",
    },
    {
      "question": "finance",
      "answer": "資助",
    },
    {
      "question": "indigent",
      "answer": "貧窮",
    },
    {
      "question": "bidding",
      "answer": "競標",
    },
    {
      "question": "lease",
      "answer": "租約",
    },
    {
      "question": "redress",
      "answer": "救濟",
    },
    {
      "question": "deficit",
      "answer": "赤字",
    },
    {
      "question": "levy",
      "answer": "徵收",
    },
    {
      "question": "ration",
      "answer": "定量",
    },
    {
      "question": "rebate",
      "answer": "回扣",
    },
    {
      "question": "merchandise",
      "answer": "商品",
    },
    {
      "question": "enterprise",
      "answer": "企業",
    },
    {
      "question": "currency",
      "answer": "貨幣",
    },
    {
      "question": "tariff",
      "answer": "關稅",
    },
    {
      "question": "consume",
      "answer": "消耗",
    },
    {
      "question": "disburse",
      "answer": "支付",
    },
    {
      "question": "acting",
      "answer": "代理的",
    },
    {
      "question": "inertia",
      "answer": "惰性",
    },
    {
      "question": "audit",
      "answer": "審査",
    },
    {
      "question": "shipment",
      "answer": "裝載",
    }
  ]
}
